# DANIEL FLORES GUERRERO

### Jr. Software Developer

1874 Rue Saint-Clement Montreal, QC H1V3E6 (514)-730-7996

daniellesifg@gmail.com - www.gitlab.com/Danielifg - www.github.com/Danielifg - www.linkedin.com/in/Danielifg

Software developer with more than one-year of experience working with Java web-based and SOA applications. Full stack developer devoted to the user experience as means of the entire application. Disciplined and passionate to learn new technologies as well as capable to work in high-stress and fast-paced environment.

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

- **CLIENT SIDE:** JSF Primefaces, Bootfaces ,PrimeNG, RichFaces themes & components, Ajax, ES6, jQuery, ReactJs, Bootstrap, Zurb Foundation.
- SERVER SIDE: Java 8, Java EE 6, JPA, Hibernate, MySQL Server, Glassfish Server, Maven Python3, Flask web framework, Python open computer vision, Python moviepy library, Amazon EC2 instance, Docker.
- OPERATING SYSTEMS: Unix like, Windows 10 Pro, Linux Debian like, Ubuntu Server.

### **EXPERIENCE**

FiloWifi Solutions Inc. MTL ,QC.

2017-06 to 2018-02

Software Developer

Project 1: Social Login website for WiFi hotspot, Atlantic city, NJ, USA.

- Successfully deployed login and management portal for user data from free wifi network, Atlantic City, NJ beach boardwalk.
- Achieved a 30% increase of users during the first two weeks of deployment via marketing promotions on the site.

Project 2: Emergency Messaging System, Atlantic city, NJ, USA.

 Collaborated with local police department providing a browser interface to beach boardwalk LED screens for emergency messages.

Project 3: People Counting Application, Atlantic city, NJ, USA.

- Developed command line program to count people on video surveillance records.
- Created statistics of people looking at advertisements for marketing purposes.

Project 4: Ubuntu Linux Server Setup for testing of networking hardware.

 Managed Kernel Based Virtual Machine infrastructure to host Wireless LAN controllers and simple network management protocol (SNMP) servers.

AXDEV Group Inc. MTL QC.

2015-01 to 2015-06

Project Manager Assistant.

- Migrated PDF internal database to relational database server.
- Optimized DB user experience with Java web-based application.

# **EDUCATION**

Udacity Web Platform. ReactJs NanoDegree.

2017-12 to present

Concordia University. Diploma in Java Application Development.

2016-06 to 2017-06

McGill University. International Exchange co-op program.

2015-01 to 2015-06

Monterrey Institute of Technology and Higher Education. Mexico.
B.A. in International commerce.

2010-05 to 2015-12

Languages: English, French, Spanish.